

hariyaniankita3@gmail.com

Ahmedabad, Gujarat

Ankita Hariyani

Senior Marketing Executive

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Hold 4+ years of experience as a Content Writer with a demonstrated history of working in the IT industry. Have technical precision, business experience to compose clear and technically detailed write-ups with ease to market products and services.

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Analytical Thinking

Problem Solving

Flexible

Strong Communication

Team Player



Learning to Write Marketing Copy July 2020

Writing a Compelling Blog Post July 2020



INTERNSHIPS & PROJECTS

SIP

Summer Internship Project
Individual Financial Planning

CP

Comprehensive Project

Performance Evaluation of Mutual Funds

GCR

Global Country Report

Study on Retail Industries in Hongkong

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE



Volansys Technologies

Senior Marketing Executive, June 2020-Present

- Writing clear marketing copy to promote our products/services.
- Developing content for blogs, press release, success story, product descriptions, social media, and the company website.
- Generating ideas for new content types and proofreading articles before publication
- Coordinate with marketing and design teams to illustrate images.
- Coordinate with SEO team for keyword research and use SEO guidelines to increase web traffic.
- Ensure all-around consistency (style, fonts, images, and tone)
- Update website content as needed.
- Preparing format/guidelines for the required collaterals

Cygnet Infotech

Marketing Executive, June 2018-June 2020

- Develop engaging content for website blogs.
- Prepare other collaterals such as E-book,
 Presentation content, Video Scripts,
 Infographics, Success stories, Press release,
 Website content etc.
- Hands on experience on Visme tool for rolling out quick presentations.
- Perform ad hoc tasks required by the sales team such as presentation, case studies or proposals.
- Add graphics, use cases/illustrations to elaborate the concept or condense complicated information into easily digestible articles.
- Ensure that content contains sufficient keywords for search engine optimization.
- Meet and discuss with subject matter experts for authenticated and verified technical write-ups.
- Editing and proofreading content.

.

Sinclair Digitech

Content Writer, Jan 2018 - May 2018

- Responsible for delivering content for client's website.
- Technical Guest blogging on weekly basis.
- Managing client's website for blogging.
- Social Media promotion activities for clients.
- Company's website blog writing.

Infinium Solutionz (Amnex Info technologies)

Content Writer, May 2017 - Nov 2017

- Responsible for developing content for brochures and website.
- Assigned the task of writing quality content for blogs and newsletter.
- Handled the task of editing and proof-reading content before publishing.
- Coordinating with third party for brochure designing.

Verve Systems

BDE & Content Writer, Sept 2016 - April 2017

- Identifying, researching and targeting new business prospects.
- Market Research, Data collection, Lead Generation, cold calling
- B2B and B2C sales exposure
- Gaining new appointments through emails and B2B market research Strategy,
- Content writing, Blog writing and Social media marketing

Arvaan Technolab

Business Development Executive, Jan 2015 – March 2016

- Identifying, researching, and targeting new business prospects.
- Liaising with new and existing clients over the Skype.
- Gaining new appointments through emailing and B2B market research strategy.
- managing and maintaining databases of the potential clients.
- Developing strong working relationships with prospective new clients.
- Producing monthly pipeline reports for management purpose.
- B2B and B2C sales exposure, requirement analysis, Online bidding on various portals (Guru, Elance, Upwork, People per Hour).

EDUCATION



L.J Institute of Management Studies, Ahmedabad *Executive MBA, GPA 7.2, 2014*

L.J College of Computer Application, Ahmedabad

Bachelor of Computer Application (BCA), 64%, 2012

K.P.E.S English School, Bhavnagar

HSC (Science), 62%, 2009

K.P.E.S English School, Bhavnagar

SSC, 84.31%, 2007